[{"question":"which object is bigger?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The porcelain cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The leather cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"What is the material of the small cube?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"Bamboo"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"Metal"}],"answer":1},{"question":"How many cubes there?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"3"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"4"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object has larger density?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The small leather cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The small metal cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Is the medium porcelain cube heavier than the small leather cube?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object has lower restitution?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The small leather cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The medium porcelain cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which quadrant will the small metal cube be in when it finally stops moving ?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"\u2160"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"\u2161"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"\u2162"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"\u2163"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which quadrant will the medium porcelain cube be in when it finally stops moving ?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"\u2160"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"\u2161"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"\u2162"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"\u2163"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object will stop moving earlier?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The small metal cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The small leather cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which object will stop moving first?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The medium porcelain cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The small leather cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Will the medium porcelain cube travel to quadrant \u2163?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Will there a collision in the quadrant \u2162?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1},{"question":"How many collisions will happen between objects?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"<=3"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":">3"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Will the medium porcelain cube collide more than once?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the small leather cube collide with the medium porcelain cube in this video?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the small metal cube collide with the small leather cube in this video?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which objects is the first collision?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The medium porcelain cube and the small leather cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The wall and the small metal cube"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"The wall and the medium porcelain cube"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"The medium porcelain cube and the small metal cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which objects is the last collision?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The wall and the small metal cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The medium porcelain cube and the wall"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"The wall and the small leather cube"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"The medium porcelain cube and the small metal cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Will the small metal cube collide with other objects after it stops moving?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1}]